<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<settings>
	<title>Flip Card</title>
	<directionsTextVer>Answer the following questions. Select each flip card to review the answer.</directionsTextVer>
	<width>180</width>
	<height>185</height>
	<bgcolor>#bebebe</bgcolor>
	<speed>350</speed>
	<spinDirection>lr</spinDirection>
	<customTextVer><!--interactives/02_03_06/textversion.htm--></customTextVer>
  
	<flipcard>
	  <cardfront>
	  	<title></title>
		<text><![CDATA[<p>What are the Chinese New Year traditions in Karen’s family that are similar to Kailan’s?</p>]]></text>
		<img>
		  <alt></alt>
		  <description></description>
		  <src></src>
		</img>
	  </cardfront>
	  <cardback>
	  	<title></title>
	    <text><![CDATA[<p>Both families have the New Year’s Eve family dinner and put up couplets and lanterns, and children receive red packets from adults in the family.</p>]]></text>
		<img>
		  <alt></alt>
		  <description></description>
		  <src></src>
		</img>
	  </cardback>
	</flipcard>
	
	<flipcard>
	  <cardfront>
	    <title></title>
	    <text><![CDATA[<p>What are some Chinese traditions that Karen’s family observe during Christmas or any other Western holidays?</p>]]></text>
		<img>
		  <alt></alt>
		  <description></description>
		  <src></src>
		</img>
	  </cardfront>
	  <cardback>
	  	<title></title>
	    <text><![CDATA[<p>They observe the Chinese traditions, such as adults giving red packets or presents to children, having family dinners, and visiting relatives.</p>]]></text>
		<img>
		  <alt></alt>
		  <description></description>
		  <src></src>
		</img>
	  </cardback>
	</flipcard>
	
	<flipcard>
	  <cardfront>
	    <title></title>
	    <text><![CDATA[<p>Who takes care of Karen’s maternal grandparents?</p>]]></text>
		<img>
		  <alt></alt>
		  <description></description>
		  <src></src>
		</img>
	  </cardfront>
	  <cardback>
	  	<title></title>
	    <text><![CDATA[<p>Her maternal grandparents live in a senior home with a pension. Her mom and her siblings take turns visiting them and taking care of financial matters when needed.</p>]]></text>
		<img>
		  <alt></alt>
		  <description></description>
		  <src></src>
		</img>
	  </cardback>
	</flipcard>
	<flipcard>
	  <cardfront>
	    <title></title>
	    <text><![CDATA[<p>Did Karen’s great-grandparents date before they got married, and how is it different from Kailan’s great-grandparents?</p>]]></text>
		<img>
		  <alt></alt>
		  <description></description>
		  <src></src>
		</img>
	  </cardfront>
	  <cardback>
	  	<title></title>
	    	<text><![CDATA[<p>Karen’s great-grandparents dated and wrote love letters to each other before they got married. Kailan’s great-grandparents didn’t date or even touch each other’s hands before they got married.</p>]]></text>
		<img>
		  <alt></alt>
		  <description></description>
		  <src></src>
		</img>
	  </cardback>
	</flipcard>

</settings>